A woman is seen walking in the streets of Tokyo.
Uma mulher é vista a caminhar pelas ruas de Tóquio.
the streets look wet on a night that seems to be a weekend night by the atmosphere that is observed
as ruas parecem molhadas numa noite que parece ser de fim de semana pela atmosfera
she wears the latest fashion
ela usa as últimas modas
the detail and quality of the video looks spectacular.
o detalhe e a qualidade do vídeo são espectaculares.
and of repetente.......
e de repetente.......
it reaches your ears that this is not a video shooting...
é de notar que isto não é uma filmagem de vídeo...
but it is generated by an artificial intelligence through the input of a prompt
mas é gerado por uma inteligência artificial através da entrada de um prompt
It's called Sora, and it's from the company Open AI.
Chama-se Sora e é da empresa Open AI.
at the moment it lacks the capability to generate audio to accompany the video
De momento, não tem a capacidade de gerar áudio para acompanhar o vídeo.
however, it is currently being trained on it and very soon it will be able to implement sound according to the video it has constructed
No entanto, está atualmente a ser treinado para isso e em breve será capaz de implementar som para acompanhar o vídeo que construiu.
incredible advances that will bring great consequences for the cinematographic world.
avanços incríveis que terão enormes consequências disruptivas para o mundo do cinema.
Will it be able to generate motion pictures in just a few seconds and at no cost to .....?
Será capaz de gerar filmes de cinema em apenas alguns segundos e sem custos para .....?
The future is uncertain, but human beings have always been able to navigate through the mists of uncertainty and emerge successful...
O futuro é incerto, mas os seres humanos sempre foram capazes de navegar através das brumas da incerteza e emergir com sucesso...
subtitles by Cristian Varela Casas Video activity of DIW Web 2023-2024 Translated with DeepL.com (free version)
legendas por Cristian Varela Casas Atividade de vídeo do DIW Web 2023-2024